저녁 때 새로운 거 먹을까?
You feel like trying
something new for dinner?
인도 요리?
텍스 멕스?
Maybe Indian, Tex-Mex?
인간이 포유류가 아닌
You ever wonder how
humans would be different
도마뱀으로부터
진화했다면 어땠을까?
if they evolved from lizards
instead of mammals?
그 주제로 넘어갔군
Okay, let's talk
about that.
도마뱀은 냉혈 파충류라
As you know, lizards--
cold-blooded animals--
스스로 체열을 낼 수 없어
lack the ability to
sense temperature.
추울 때는
더 느리게 움직인지
But they do move more
sluggishly when it's cold.
기상캐스터 도마뱀은
이렇게 말할 거야
So, lizard weathermen
would say things like,
스웨터를 준비하셔야겠어요,
느릿느릿한 날씨네요
"Bring a sweater,
it's slow outside."
내 사고방식이 너무 좋다
I love my mind.
모두들 팬이야
We all do.
암튼 저녁은 뭐 먹을래?
Now, how about dinner?
곤충이나 더 작은
도마뱀을 먹겠지
Oh, I would assume we'd enjoy
insects or smaller lizards.
서로의 꼬리를 뽑아서
구워먹어도 되겠다
We could also pull each other's
tails off and grill them;
다시 자랄 테니까
they'll just grow back.
Oh!
미스터 스팍
세움간판이 도착했다
My life-size cardboard
Mr. Spock is here!
인간적 감정의 표출을
바라지 않겠지만
I know he wouldn't care for
an outburst of human emotion,
신난다!
but, oh, goodie, oh,
goodie, oh, goodie.
스팍 중령, 펼쳐질 수 있게
승인 부탁합니다
Commander Spock requesting
permission to be unfolded.
실례할게
Excuse me.
승인되었습니다
Permission granted, Commander.
그러니까 똑똑한 원숭이일수록
Which is why the more
intelligent the monkey,
변을 더 많이
집어던지는 거야
the more feces they fling.
에이미, 잠시 끼어들게
(knocks)
Excuse me, Amy.
페니, 오늘 저녁에
시간 어때?
Penny, do you have plans
for dinner tonight?
애들이랑 어디 가기로 했어?
Why, you guys going somewhere?
아니, 우리 둘만
No, I mean just you and me.
데이트처럼?
You mean, like a date?
데이트처럼은 아니고,
데이트야
Not like a date, a date.
Ooh...!
그래
Um... o-okay.
그러지 뭐
Sure.
Ooh...!
SHELDON:
Oh, no!
잘못된 스팍을 보냈네
They sent the wrong Spock!
오래 살고 꺼져라,
재커리 퀸토
Live long and suck it,
Zachary Quinto.
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x13
The Recombination Hypothesis
Original Air Date on January 19, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
너무 신난다
This is so exciting.
레너드랑 페니가
다시 합치면
If Leonard and Penny
get back together,
우리 커플이랑
더블 데이트하면 되잖아
Howard and I can go on
double dates with them.
나랑 쉘든은 어쩌고?
How come you never invite
Sheldon and me on a double date?
Mm, uh...
페니, 아직 멀었어?
How's it going
in there, Penny?!
잠깐
PENNY:
Just a sec.
너무 과한가?
Too much?
- 응
- 아니
Yes.
No.
좀 기다려봐
Okay, just hang on.
성적 매력을
감상할 줄 모르는군
You just can't handle
her raw sexuality, can you?
레너드랑 언제 깨졌어?
When did you and Leonard
break up?
2년 전
Uh, about two years ago.
왜 갑자기 불러내는 거지?
Why do you think
he asked you out again?
모르겠어
I don't know.
죽을 병에 걸렸을 수도 있어
Maybe he's dying.
너무 낭만적이겠다
That would be so romantic.
레너드는 건강해
He's not dying.
안됐다
Too bad.
죽을 병이라면
침대에 눕히고
If he were, she could just
throw him in bed
숨이 넘어갈 때까지
앞뒤로 흔들면 되는데
and ride him
right up until he flatlines.
이건 어때?
How about this?
- 괜찮을 수도
- 그건 아니다
Maybe.
Come on.
Yeah, okay, no.
오늘 외박할 거야?
Do you think
you'll sleep with him tonight?
절대 그럴 일 없어
PENNY:
Absolutely not.
일단은 저녁만 먹고
Look, we're just
gonna have dinner
어떻게 되는지 봐야지
and, you know,
see how it goes.
죽을 병에 걸렸다면
같이 잘 생각 있어?
If he were dying,
would you sleep with him?
뭐?
What?!
성병이 아니라는 가정 하에
Assuming he were
dying of something
that couldn't be
sexually transmitted.
머리에 창이 꽂혀서
죽어간다고 치자
You know, like a spear wound
to the head.
레너드는 안 죽어
Okay, he is not dying.
어떻게 알아?
네가 의사야?
How do you know?
Are you a doctor?
상상은 할 수 있잖아
You can make-believe, though.
하워드가 부정맥을 앓고 있고
Sometimes Howard and I pretend
that his arrhythmia is acting up
나는 섹시한 심장병
전문의라고 상상하기도 해
and I'm a sexy cardiologist.
재밌는 건 내가
당담의사가 아니라는 거야
And the naughty part is
I'm not in his HMO network.
오바하지 않을 거야
Screw it. I'm not gonna
make a big deal out of this.
그냥 저녁만 먹는 거잖아
It's just dinner.
죽어가는 남자랑
With a dead man.
(growls playfully)
에이미, 그만해
Amy, stop it.
너무 긴장된다
Oh, God, I'm so nervous.
진정해
BERNADETTE:
Relax.
레너드는 항상
널 좋아했잖아
You know Leonard's
always been crazy about you.
잘 될 거야
It's gonna be great.
드디어 어색하지
않은 사이가 됐는데
I know, but we've finally
gotten to a place
where we can hang out
without it being weird.
뭔가 잘못되면 어쩌지?
And what if something
goes wrong? Then what?
그럼 더블데이트는
나랑 쉘든이 하겠네
Guess it'll just
be Sheldon and me
going on a double date
with Howard and Bernadette.
그러면 좋겠다
Sure, we'd love that.
옷 갈아입자,
내 운명이 걸려있어
Change your clothes;
we got a lot riding on this.
Mm...
길을 만들고 싶은데
I want to build a road,
나무가 필요해
but I need wood.
너네는 나무 있어?
Do either of you fellows
have wood?
왜 웃는지 이해가 안돼
I don't understand the laughter.
'카탄'은 길을 만들고
개척하는 게임이잖아
The object of Settlers of Catan
is to build roads
and settlements.
그러려면 나무가 필요하고
To do so requires wood.
양은 있고 나무가 필요해
Now, I have sheep; I need wood.
양이랑 나무 교환할 사람?
Who has wood for my sheep?
(both laughing)
어때?
Okay, how do I look?
그것보다 대체
왜 이러는 거야?
More to the point, why
are you doing this?
무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
페니랑 끝난 거 아냐?
Did you forget
what Penny did to you?
2년이나 마음고생하고
내 동생까지 더럽혔잖아
It took you two years
and defiling my sister
이제야 잊었나 싶었는데
to turn that frown upside down.
더럽히다니,
사귄 거였어
I didn't defile your sister,
we had a relationship.
'브라운 슈거'라고 부르더라
I heard you call her
Brown Sugar.
내 기준으로는
더럽히는 거야
In my book,
that's defilement.
내 의견도 말해줄까?
You want to know my opinion?
제발 말해줘
Oh, boy, do I!
비꼬는 건가?
Sarcasm?
아니
No.
그럼 말해줄게
All right, then.
네가 페니의
백치미에 끌리는 건
The reason you're fixated on
a good-natured simpleton
like Penny is that
첫 관계와 정반대
성향이기 때문이지
she's the exact opposite of
your first romantic attachment:
훌륭하지만 위협적인
엄마라는 존재
your brilliant
yet intimidating mother.
그건 어디서 나온 생각이야?
Where on earth
did you get that from?
너네 엄마가 책을 냈어,
'애정결핍 아이의 욕심 채우기'
It's in her book,
Needy Baby, Greedy Baby.
그렇다고 사실은 아니잖아
That doesn't make it true.
논픽션으로 분류되어 있거든
It's called nonfiction
for a reason, Leonard.
이따 보자
See you later.
그 책을 영화화하면
If they ever make
a movie version
레너드 엄마 역에
딱인 배우가 있어
of that book, you know who
should play Leonard's mother?
산드라 블록
Sandra Bullock.
왜?
Why?
모든 면에서 완벽하니까
Because she's great
in everything.
무슨 얘기하고 있었지?
Now, where were we?
맞다,
나무 있냐고?
Oh, yes.
Does anyone have any wood?
(both snickering)
Oh, come on!
나무가 필요한 것 뿐이야
I just want wood.
너무 딱딱하게 굴지 마
Why are you making it so hard?
(both laughing)
전에 사귀던 사람과
첫 데이트를 뭐라고 부르지?
So, do they have a name
for a first date
with someone
you used to go out with?
좋은 질문이야
Oh, that's a good question.
어색하다고 표현하면 맞겠지
How about "awkward"?
적합하네
Yeah, that sounds right.
Yeah?
처음 만난 사이라고
상상하면 어떨까?
Hey, how about if we pretend
we're actually on a first date?
어떤지 보자
See how that goes.
그래
Okay.
(clears throat)
폴리, 그쪽에 대해
더 알고 싶어요
So, Polly,
tell me about yourself.
(chuckles)
페니라고 해요
It's Penny.
미안해요,
분위기가 어색하네요
Oh, sorry, yeah.
Awkward.
(laughs)
Okay, uh, let's see.
네브라스카 출신이고
어릴 적부터 꿈이 있었어요
I'm from Nebraska, and ever
since I was a little girl,
LA에 와서
영화배우가 되고 싶었죠
I dreamed of moving to L.A.
and becoming a movie star.
Anyway,
4년 동안 연기 수업을 듣고
서빙 알바를 하면서
after four years of acting
lessons and waiting tables,
치핵 광고도 찍고
I've done
a hemorrhoid commercial
허접한 촬영소에서
안네프랭크 역을 맡았어요
and a production of Anne Frank
above a bowling alley.
(chuckles)
꿈은 이루어져요
So, you know,
dreams do come true.
네 차례야
Your turn.
어디 보자
Uh, let's see.
(clears throat)
칼텍 실험 물리학자이고요
Uh, I am an experimental
physicist at Cal-Tech,
고출력 레이저를 다뤄요
most of my research is
with high-powered lasers,
얼마 전 정부
지원금을 받았는데
and, oh, I've just gotten
a big government grant
레이저로 탄도 미사일을
막으려는 과제에요
to see if they can be used
to knock out
incoming ballistic missiles.
가능한가요?
Wow. Can they?
그럴 리가요
Oh, God, no.
수입은 짭잘해요
The money's pretty good.
장비로 배트시그널을
만들기도 해요
And I used the equipment
to make my own Bat-signal.
(laughs)
배트시그널?
Bat-signal?
무슨 괴짜처럼 들리네요
What are you, some kind of nerd?
그냥 괴짜가 아니라
괴짜 천재입니다
Not some kind of nerd,
I'm the king of the nerds.
(laughs)
그건 또 무슨 소리에요?
What does that mean?
마음에 안 드는
사람이 있으면
Uh, it means
if anyone displeases me,
프린터 설치를
안 도와준다는 거죠
I don't help them
set up their printer.
(laughs)
너무 재밌다
You are so funny.
다행이군요
Good.
셔츠를 벗어도
그렇게 기억해줘요
Remember that
when I take my shirt off.
(both laugh)
레너드,
너무 즐겁다
Leonard, this is nice.
불러줘서 고마워
I'm so glad we did this.
Me, too.
어때?
So what do you think?
다시 만날까?
Are we gonna get back together?
그건 너무 빠르잖아
Whoa. Not so fast.
내가 뭐라고 했지?
I'm sorry, what did I say?
레너드, 난 네게
항상 감정은 있어
Leonard, you know I will always
have feelings for you.
- 제길
- 왜 그래?
Oh, God.
What?
항상이라고 했잖아
You said "always."
나한테 항상
감정이 있을 거라고
You'll always have
feelings for me.
그런데?
So?
누군가랑 관계를 원하지
않을 때 하는 소리잖아
So, that sounds more like
something you'd say
if you didn't want
a relationship with someone.
우리는 안되겠다
"This isn't working out,
하지만 난 항상 좋은
감정을 갖고 있을 거야
but I'll always have
feelings for you."
네 친구랑 자서 미안해
"I'm sorry I slept
with your best friend,
하지만 난 항상 좋은
감정을 갖고 있을 거야
but I'll always have
feelings for you."
리사, 문제는 이거야
"Here's the thing, Lisa,
네게는 항상 좋은 감정이
있었지만 나는 게이야
I'm into dudes now, but I'll
always have feelings for you."
그럼 넌 어떻게
표현할 건데?
How would you say it?
나는 네게 감정이 있어
I have feelings for you.
- 똑같잖아
- 아냐
It's the same thing.
No, it's not.
'항상'을 넣으면 달라져
"Always" made it worse.
넌 생각이 너무 많아
You're overthinking this.
- 아냐
- 맞거든
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
넌 항상 이런 식이야
You always overthink things.
또 그러네,
'항상'을 집어넣지 마
Th-There you go.
"Always" made it worse.
우리 사이에는 대화를
나누면 일이 터져
See, this is where everything
goes wrong: when we talk.
대화를 나누지 않으면
관계를 갖을 수 없어
Well, I don't know how you have
a relationship without talking.
전에 TJ라는 남자를 만났는데
Hey, I went out with this guy TJ
8달 동안 말도 안했어
for eight months,
we never talked.
아직까지도 TJ가
무엇의 약자인지 몰라
To this day, I don't even know
what TJ stands for.
얘기를 안했다면 그럼...
Wait, if you guys
didn't talk, what--
됐다,
바보같은 질문이야
Never mind, stupid question.
이제 나무가 있으니
And now that I have
some wood,
마을을 세우기 시작해야지
I'm going to begin
the erection of my settlement.
일부러 그러는 거지?
He's got to be
doing this on purpose.
(laughs)
오, 8시30분이네
Ooh, 8:30.
페니랑 신나게 놀았어?
You and Penny decide to go out
and paint the town beige?
넌 30살인데
엄마랑 살고 있잖아
You're 30 years old
and you live with your mother.
잘 안 풀렸나봐
I guess it didn't go well.
그건 모르지
We don't know that.
확신을 갖을 수는 없어
Not to a certainty.
레너드가
돌아왔다는 것만 알아
All we know
is that Leonard is home.
(Leonard screams)
지금은 어때?
How about now?
아직 증거가
충분치 않아
Again, not enough
evidence.
살해당하고 있을 수 있지
For all we know,
he's being murdered.
게임이나 하자
Now, back to our game.
넌 뭔가를 세우고 있었지
You were in the middle
of an erection.
그렇지,
내가 잡고 있네
Oh, of course.
It's right here in my hand.
(cell phone chimes)
(grunting quietly)
뭘 원하는 거지?
What does she want from me now?
무슨 일이야?
What's up?
너무 복잡하게
생각 하지 마
Do not overthink this.
이해가 안돼
I don't understand.
Bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup.
아까는 내가 볼 때...
Okay, but earlier
it seemed like...
얘기는 그만
No talking.
하는 도중에도?
가끔 궁금한 게 있어서
Even during? 'Cause
sometimes I have questions.
(panting)
재밌네
Well, that was fun.
발에 쥐가 나긴 했지만
Yeah, except for when I got
the foot cramp.
잘 버텼어
You hung in there, though.
많은 게 걸려 있었지
There was a lot at stake.
이제는 뭐할래?
So what do you
want to do now?
천식 호흡기를
갖고 오고 싶은데
Well, I want to go get
my asthma inhaler,
분위기를 깰까봐
but it might ruin the moment.
(grunts)
이해 좀 시켜줘
Just, just
help me out here.
데이트는 망했는데
어떻게 섹스로 끝나지?
How does a miserable date
end in sex?
몰라, 복잡해
I don't know,
it's complicated.
난 머리가 좋은 남자야
Well, I'm
a pretty smart guy,
그리고 지금은 뇌에
피 공급이 잘 되고 있어
and right now my brain has
dibs on the blood supply,
한번 설명해봐
so give it a go.
알았어
Okay, it's just,
레스토랑에서 다시
만나자고 할때
at the restaurant
when you said
you wanted us to
be together again,
너무 진도가 빠른 것
같아서 무서웠어
it got very real very
fast and I panicked.
왜?
Why?
뭐가 그렇게 두려워?
What are you
afraid of?
우리가 다시 사귀면
Well, what if
we do go out
내가 또 바보 짓을 하고
헤어지자고 할 수 있잖아
and I do something stupid
and dump you again?
내가 찰 수도 있지
What if I dump you?
(scoffs)
농담이 아냐
Come on, be serious.
그럼 사귀는 사이라고
생각하지 말고
Well, how about
if we don't think
about this
as a relationship?
소프트웨어의 새로운
버전이라 생각하자
It could be more like
a new version of software.
페니와 레너드 2.0
Penny and Leonard 2.0.
시범 운영을 하고,
버그를 잡고
We can test it internally,
shake out the bugs,
괜찮다 싶으면
and if we both feel
it's solid,
공개하는 거지
then we'll roll it out
to the public.
그럼 비밀로 하는 거야?
So we don't tell people
we're back together?
그렇지
Exactly.
잘 안 풀린 척하면 되지
We pretend like our date
went badly.
그건 사실이고
Well, we don't really
have to pretend.
그냥 친구로 남기로
했다고 하면 돼
And we let them think
that we decided
to just be friends
어색하지 않은 사이로
and that everything's cool.
좋아
Okay, great.
(grunts softly)
방금 기억났어
Hey, I just remembered.
네 호흡기 아직 있어
I still got one
of your inhalers.
아직도 갖고 있었어?
I can't believe
you kept this.
응, 못 버리겠더라
Yeah, I was gonna throw it
away, but I just couldn't.
감동적이다
That is so sweet.
(sighs)
25~30분 후 이게 얼마나
중요한지 알게 될 거야
In 25 to 30 minutes
I'm gonna show you
how much
this means to me.
(toilet flushes)
레너드?
Leonard?
안녕
Yeah, hi, hi.
잘 지내?
How's it going?
나쁘지는 않아
Uh, can't complain.
물어봐줘서 고마워
Thanks for asking.
새벽 3시에 뭐하는 거야?
Well, what were you doing out
at 3:00 in the morning?
넌 왜 일어났는데?
Well, uh, uh...
what are you doing up?
화장실 쓰고 있었어
I was using the bathroom.
나도 그래
Yeah, well, so was I.
그래?
Really?
널 못 봤는데
I didn't see you in there.
네가 쓰고 있어서
Obviously... when I saw
that you were in ours,
다른 화장실 썼지
I went and used another one.
어디?
Where?
건너편 주유소에서
The, the gas station
across the street.
잠옷을 입고?
In your pajamas?
응
Yes.
맨발로?
Without shoes?
응
Yes.
이렇게 추운 겨울밤에?
On a cold
winter's night?
응
Yes.
좀 말이 안 된다
Seems unlikely.
호흡기는 갖고 갔어?
Did you bring
your asthma inhaler?
응
Uh, uh, uh, yes, I did.
그럼 가능한 것 같네
Well, then,
I guess it's plausible.
이봐
D-- hang on a
second, mister.
뭐?
What?
주유소 화장실을 쓰고
After you used the facilities
at the gas station,
뭔가 구입은 했어?
did you make a purchase?
What?
주유소 화장실을 썼으면
It's customary, when
using the restroom
뭔가 샀을 거 아냐
at a retail establishment,
to make a small purchase.
샀어?
Did you?
아니
No.
(scoffs)
여기 2달러 줄게
Here's two dollars.
소고기 육포나 사 먹어
Go buy some beef jerky.
소고기 육포 싫은데
I don't want beef jerky.
그건 중요하지 않아
It's not about you.
파키스탄에서 온
가난한 알바생이
It's about a poor immigrant
from Pakistan
아메리칸 드림을
이루기 위해
trying to make his way
in America
셰브러너 주유소에서
야간 알바를 뛰고 있잖아
by working the graveyard shift
at the Colorado Boulevard
Chevron.
알았어
Fine.
애정결핍 아이가
욕심이 많다고 했잖아
Needy Baby, Greedy Baby indeed.
레너드 곧 올 거야
Leonard will be here
in a moment.
다른 주차 공간을 찾고 있어
He's looking
for a different parking space.
왜?
Why?
'손주에 대해 물어보세요'
스티커를 붙인 차 옆에 대서
We were next to a car
with an "Ask me about my
grandchildren" bumper sticker,
나갈 때 마주치게 되면
and I was afraid if we ran
into them on the way out,
의무적으로
물어봐야할 것 같아서
I'd be obligated
to do so.
페니랑 잘 안 풀려서
너무 실망이다
I'm so disappointed it didn't
work with him and Penny.
나도
Me, too.
남을 배려하는 마음으로
Out of deference
to them,
우리의 행복한 관계를
자랑하지는 말자
let's not flaunt our
happy relationship.
넌 인간 감정을
잘 알고 있네
You have a keen insight
into the human heart,
에이미 패러 파울러
Amy Farrah Fowler.
고어/리버맨 스티커를 붙인
스바루 옆에 주차했어
We are next to a Suburu with
a Gore/Lieberman bumper sticker.
그쪽에서 정치 얘기를
하고 싶지는 않을 거야
Well, I doubt they'd want to
talk about that, so we're fine.
페니랑 잘 안 풀렸는데도
I'm surprised to see you here
여기에 오다니 의외네
after it went
so badly with Penny.
우린 성인이잖아
Well, hey, we're grown-ups.
친구로 지낼 수 있어
We can still be friends.
난 하워드랑 깨지면
친구로 못 지낼 거 같아
Boy, I don't know if I
could be friends with Howie
if we broke up.
왜?
Why not?
난 복수심이 강해
I'm a very vengeful person.
그래?
Really?
무기화된 천연두
바이러스도 있어
With access
to weaponized smallpox.
우선 컵부터 채워줄게
Here you go, guys, let me get
you going with some water.
메뉴 필요해?
아니면 이미 정했나?
You need menus
or you know what you want?
레너드는
뭘 원하는지 아는데
Leonard knows what he wants,
but it looks
너한테서는
못 받을 것 같네
like he's not gonna
get it from you.
하워드
Howard.
No,
괜찮아, 베르나데트
that's okay, Bernadette.
가끔은 안 풀릴 때가 있지
Sometimes these things
just don't work out.
우리는 괜찮아
Yeah, it's all good.
서로에게 항상 좋은
감정을 갖고 있을 거야
We-We'll always have
feelings for each other.
거 참 다행이네
Oh, that's nice.
'항상'의 뜻이 이렇다고
See, she knew
what "always" meant.
이런 건 절대
안 놓치는구나
Wow, you're like a dog
with a bone, aren't you?
그냥 증명하는 거야
I'm just making a point.
네가 얼마나 집착하는지?
Is the point that you don't know
when to let something go?
얘들아
People, people,
너네 둘이 뭔가
후회스러운 말을 하기 전에
please,
before you say
something you
both regret,
난 주문을 하고 싶어
I'd like to place my order.
기다려봐, 쉘든
Yeah, just hang on, Sheldon.
우리는 왜 안 되는지 알아?
You know why we can't be
together?
넌 항상 네가
옳다고 생각하니까
Because you always have
to be right.
그건 사실이 아냐
Oh, that is not true.
레너드 편을 들어야겠다
I got to go
with Leonard on this.
내가 아는 누구보다도
틀린 말을 많이 해
He is wrong
more than anyone I know.
그러고 보니
난 휴식 시간이다
You know what?
I just realized I'm on a break.
다른 사람 부를게
I'll get someone else.
Well...
새로운 웨이트리스가 오면
이것만 약속해줘
Leonard, promise me that when
our new waitress comes over,
만났다 깨졌다 하는
관계를 시작하지 않겠다고
you will not start a complicated
on-again, off-again relationship
나는 매우 배고프니까
with her,
because I am very, very hungry.
(grunting quietly)
(phone chimes)
이럴 수가
Unbelievable.
레스토랑에서
왜 그렇게 대했어?
Mind explaining to me
why you were being
such a jerk at the restaurant?
Well,
다시 안 만나기로
했으니까 연기한 거야
I was trying to act like
we weren't seeing each other.
그럴 계획 아니였어?
That was the plan, right?
No,
친구로 남기로
하는 계획이였지
the plan was to tell people
we decided to stay friends.
네가 항상 이렇게
바보처럼 굴면 어렵다고
That's a little hard to do
when you're always being
such a tool bag.
난 더 이상 이런
헛소리 듣고 싶지 않아
You know what? I don't have to
stand here and take this crap.
대체 어디 가는 거야?
The hell do you think
you're going?
싸운 다음에
섹스하는 거 아냐?
Isn't sex after fighting
kind of what we do now?!
맞아, 그렇지
Yeah, kind of, yeah.
우리 뭐 하는 거지?
What are we doing?
무슨 말이야?
What do you mean?
우리를 상상할 때마다
좋게 끝나지 않아
Every scenario I play out
for you and me ends badly.
넌 생각이 너무
많아서 그래
That's because you
overthink everything.
레너드,
내 말 듣고 있어?
SHELDON: Leonard, are you listening
to me?
뭐?
What?
Yeah.
완전 망했어
This is a disaster.
난 레너드 니모이
세움간판을 주문했는데
I distinctly ordered
the Leonard Nimoy Mr.
Spock cardboard standee.
재커리 퀸토를 침실에
두면 날 지켜줄까?
Why would
I feel safer
with Zachary Quinto
at the foot of my bed?
'히어로즈'에서 잘 먹혔잖아
I don't know, he was
pretty badass on Heroes.
그러네,
한번 기회를 주지
You're right, I'll
give him a shot.
잠시만
Hang on.
페니, 오늘 저녁에
시간 어때?
Penny, do you have
plans for dinner?
애들이랑 어디 가기로 했어?
Why, you guys going somewhere?
아니, 우리 둘만
No, I mean just you and me.
Ooh...!
생각은 해본 거야?
Uh, have you thought
this through?
응, 그래도 가고 싶어
Yes, and I think
we should go anyway.
안 되겠다
No, can't do it.
퀸토, 넌 반품이야
Sorry, Quinto,
you're going back.
네가 레너드랑
다시 합치면
If you and Leonard
get back together,
우리 커플이랑
더블 데이트하면 되겠다
Sheldon and I
will finally have someone
to go on double dates with.
나랑 하워드는?
What about me and Howard?
너네도 끼어줄게
Fine, we can double
with you, too.
이렇게 불안해하다니
So insecure.
어디서 먹을 거야?
Where are you guys going to eat?
페니?
Penny?
신부 페니는 레너드를
신랑으로 받아들이시겠습니까?
Do you, Penny, take Leonard to
be your lawful wedded husband?
이제와서 아니라고
할 순 없잖아요
Well, it's
a little late for me
to start saying no,
isn't it?
페니
Penny.
미안, 깜박하고
약국에 안 들렸네
Sorry,
just remembered
I've got to stop
at the drugstore.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==